(Sheldon:)But whoever that mystery man was,
you should be eternally grateful...
(Sheldon:)...for without him,
there would be no Leonard's Day.
(Leonard:)Leonard's Day?
(Sheldon:)No pressure,
just get him a crummy card, you're good.
All right, test my ringtone.
(Raj:)ELTON JOHN
Rocket man
Burning out his fuse up here alone
- It really is a good song.
- Yeah, there's a reason he's Sir EIton John.
(Raj:)They don't make you a knight for writing
"Wake Me Up Before You Go-Go."
(Raj:)Howard,
are you coming down for breakfast?
(Howard:)Ma, I told you, I have a video conference
with NASA! I said don't bother me!
Ooh, listen to Mr. Big-Shot-Astronaut!
(Howard:)Yes, please listen
to Mr. Big-Shot-Astronaut!
(Howard:)Hey. Good morning.
(NASA Guy(on skype):)Hey, Howard.
Thanks for getting up so early.